notebook arc-agi-3-milestone-2.ipynb : 10 cells
cell types: {'markdown': 1, 'code': 9}
keyword cells: {'import ': 5, 'submission': 4, '/kaggle/input': 4, 'from ': 2, 'dataset': 2, 'vllm': 1, 'llm': 1}

----- cell 0 [markdown] (803 chars) -----
# TAAF ARC-AGI-3 Kaggle Run

This notebook is generated by the Tufa ARC-AGI Framework (TAAF), an open-source deployment harness from [Tufa Labs](https://tufalabs.ai/) for running ARC-AGI-3 solvers reproducibly on Kaggle.

The notebook installs the ARC runtime, makes the bundled TAAF source snapshot importable, runs any solver setup commands, loads the pickled benchmark, and writes results to `/kaggle/working`. It can run as a public/offline debug notebook or as the same code path used for competition reruns. Kaggle's `KAGGLE_IS_COMPETITION_RERUN` flag always wins and switches the run into submission mode.

For quick inline experiments, use the customization code cell just before the benchmar
    ...
